I know you're looking at me. You don't
know what what I am, okay?
I got a strange look. No one knows what
this is right away.
I'm Arab. Any Arabs in here?
[\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> THAT'S NOT GOOD for the rest of this.
>> There's a lot There's not one That's
statistically impossible, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> There's an Arab in here going, "Not
falling for that one again."
>> [laughter]
>> I am Arab. No one thinks that. Everyone
thinks I'm Jewish or lesbian, but I uh
>> [laughter]
>> I'm an Arab. It's pretty awesome. I got
an Arab mom and a white dad. Those are
very different people, okay? Very
different. An Arab mom is never pleased.
A white dad is consistently satisfied.
You could say anything to an Arab
parent, they'll find a way to be
disappointed. You know what I mean? A
white dad's always stoked. I wake up, my
dad's like, "You killed that."
>> [laughter]
>> Say anything to my mom she'd be upset
about it. I could be like, "Mom, I want
to be a nurse." She'd be like, "How
about a doctor?"
>> [laughter]
>> I could be like, "Mom, I want to be a
teacher." She'd be like, "How about a
professor?"
I could be like, "Mom, I want to be a
[\h__\h] stand-up comedian." She'd be
like, "How about a Uber driver?"
>> [laughter]
>> That ain't right.
An Arab parent will make you insecure
about flaws you didn't know you had,
okay? I put on a blonde wig the other
day. I thought that was hilarious. I
FaceTime my mom. She looked at me for
about 15 seconds and goes, "What the
[\h__\h] is wrong with your nose?"
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S A WIG.
>> I GREW UP ARAB AND WHITE, BUT MY parents
are divorced my whole life, so I did it
separately.
All right? I was Arab and white just on
different days.
It's kind of the best way to be
biracial. Now I feel like I understand
both sides pretty well. You know what I
mean? I'm Arab. I love the culture. I
appreciate the culture. I try to be a
part of the culture, but I'm also half
white, so I'm a little scared of it.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm Arab. I know that Allahu Akbar God
is great. I know that. But I'm also half
white, so I know that's not what you
hear.
>> [laughter]
>> You guys hear God is great. I'm going to
go see him and you're coming with me.
>> [laughter]
>> So I understand why you don't want to
hear it in the terminal, but they're
good people, okay?
They're great people. You got to have an
Arab in your life. You got to. An Arab
friend will have your back no matter
what. That's just the kind of person
they are, okay? My car broke down not
too long ago. My Arab friend fixed my
car. He is not a mechanic.
>> [laughter]
>> Kind of stressed me out cuz Arabs do
things their own way. You know what I
mean? Like an Arab guy will fix your
car, but you will get it back a little
bit different.
An Arab guy will be like, "The car
works. It takes diesel now."
>> [laughter]
>> "Yeah, we took out the chairs. We put in
a couch. It's nice."
>> [laughter]
>> The car will be ready for pick up.
They're like, "We got good news and bad
news about the car."
I'm like, "What's the good news?" He's
like, "Huh,
you don't owe us any money."
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like, "What's the bad news?" He's
like, "We sold it."
>> [laughter]
>> I needed that.
My mom's a funny lady. She's a smart
lady. Very smart woman. She just has big
knowledge gaps, okay? My mom has no AI
detector.
But she's addicted to social media.
Can you imagine her reality?
Just everything she sees is real all
day.
She's like, "I had no idea that Trump
was Jesus, okay?"
>> [laughter]
>> It's horrifying.
My mom sees an AI video, calls me to
panic. SHE'S LIKE, "JOSHUA, A MAN WAS
JUST EATEN ON THE SUBWAY BY AN OCTOPUS."
>> [laughter]
>> I'M LIKE, "MOM, THAT'S AI." She's like,
"How do you know?"
I'm like, "Based off what you said."
>> [laughter]
>> I know that didn't happen.
Do Do know how hard it is to defend an
octopus that you don't know?
>> [laughter]
>> I had to be like, he wouldn't do that.
I think my favorite panic call I ever
got from my mom about an AI video was
this morning. It's how I started my day.
She calls me, she's like, "Joshua, I
just saw a horrifying video. An Arab man
just shot down a helicopter from his
flying carpet."
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, "What?"
That one could be real, okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Um 50/50 on carpet guy.
My mom's a smart woman. My mom was
always the breadwinner in our family. My
mom always made the most money, which is
cool. Power to the ladies, you know what
I mean? Hell yeah. She was always the
breadwinner, which is great, but I went
to liberal arts school for college, so I
was confused the whole time.
I had no idea what anyone was talking
about. Day one of liberal arts school,
they're like, "WE NEED TO PAY WOMEN THE
SAME." I was like, "I know, they're
making way too much money, okay."
>> [laughter]
>> We got to give some to my dad, this is
[\h__\h] up.
>> [laughter]
>> I got a great dad, he taught me about
the great outdoors. I was a kayak tour
guide in San Diego, actually. I was a
kayak tour guide. Yeah, it was a it was
a sight seeing it was a sight seeing
activity.
I was a sight seeing tour guide in the
ocean. That shouldn't be a job.
The sights are there, you don't need me.
My whole job was to be like, "Look."
>> [laughter]
>> And they'd be like, "Wow."
And I'd be like, "Give me some money."
>> [laughter]
>> It's also the ocean, I don't have
control over the sights. The sights were
animals.
These people would give me all the
credit. They would see a dolphin and be
like, "Josh."
Thank you.
>> [laughter]
>> And I'd be like, "Fucking anytime."
The hardest day I ever had as a sight
seeing tour guide in the Pacific Ocean,
this is a true story. My manager came to
the back room one day and he was like,
"Josh, you're taking out two women right
now, but they're both completely blind."
And I was like,
"What the [\h__\h] are you talking about?
>> [laughter]
>> This is a sightseeing activity.
My whole job is to say, 'Look.'
>> [laughter]
>> How do I do that? He's like, "I don't
know, splash them." I'm like,
>> [laughter]
>> "What are you talking about right now?"
He's like, "Just describe the animals
that you see."
>> [laughter]
>> And I was like, "Okay."
>> These women saw more than anybody has
ever seen
in the history of the Pacific Ocean.
>> [laughter]
>> 300 blue whales.
That's a record.
There's not even that many left.
>> [laughter]
>> I didn't want to take advantage of my
power. I was like, "There's a fish."
They're like, "I love fish."
I was like, "There's a dolphin." They're
like, "That's my favorite animal." I was
like, "There's six of them."
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, "And that's Mark Cuban. We
never see him out here."
And they're like, "Wow, we did not think
we'd see that shark today."
>> [cheering]
>> What are you talking about?
The best part of that tour, truly, we
did not leave the parking lot. Okay.
[laughter]
We were in my car doing my errands for
an hour and a half of my time.
They were like, "I love the sea breeze."
I was like, "Let me know if it's too
much."
>> [laughter]
>> I love this job. We get to travel for
this job. It's the best part. I mean?
You get to do it all over the country.
It's cool. Sometimes it doesn't work
out. I was on a flight recently where
the captain sat us on the tarmac for too
long. Did that ever happen to you guys?
Hour and a half we're on the tarmac, not
one update from the captain, nothing.
Until finally he came on with the first
update. He was like, "Hey everybody, how
you doing? Uh this is your captain
speaking in the cockpit."
Which I hate when they say that.
We know.
>> [laughter]
>> If it was anybody else, it'd be a huge
[\h__\h] problem.
If someone came on like, "ALLAHU AKBAR!"
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> BUT THE CAPTAIN CAME ON HE'S LIKE,
"WE'RE HAVING A technical issue with the
airplane. We're going to have to deplane
for maintenance." And I was fine with
that, but this one lady started freaking
out. She was so pissed. She stood up.
She was like, "OH MY GOD!
[\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> YOU'RE [\h__\h] WITH MY AGENDA!"
I was like, "Your agenda?
The airplane is broken.
>> [laughter]
>> It doesn't go up.
We paid for up."
That pissed her off.
>> [laughter]
>> Very angry white woman. She started
going like this. She was like,
>> [laughter]
>> And that's how you know a white woman is
pissed.
If they start beatboxing,
>> [laughter]
>> you've struck a nerve.
I just don't know what she wanted to
hear instead.
I think she wanted to hear something
like this. Something like, "Everybody,
how you doing now? This is your captain
speaking. Uh we're having a bit of a
technical issue with the airplane right
now, but
[\h__\h] it.
>> [laughter]
>> Let's just get in the sky and see what
happens.
I got a divorce 2 days ago.
>> [laughter]
>> My kids calling me by my first name.
I'm hammered.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't work here.
Allahu Akbar.
You guys are awesome. Thank you for your
time, everyone.
>> [music]